{
    "subject": "resource/Todd_McCaffrey",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Todd McCaffrey",
    "human_readable": "Todd McCaffrey's name is Todd McCaffrey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9870221018791199,
            "question": "Is 'Todd McCaffrey' a person's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9855505228042603,
            "question": "What is Todd McCaffrey's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9068453907966614,
            "question": "What other facts could be associated with the name 'Todd McCaffrey'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8202534317970276,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Todd McCaffrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7784788012504578,
            "question": "How would you describe the information given about Todd McCaffrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6540105938911438,
            "question": "What kind of data could be linked to this statement about Todd McCaffrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6163768768310547,
            "question": "How does this statement contribute to our understanding of Todd McCaffrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10064230859279633,
            "question": "What is the purpose of stating someone's name as fact?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.033372338861227036,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the subject and the predicate in this statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02561621367931366,
            "question": "Can you think of any other examples of similar statements?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Todd McCaffrey's name is Todd McCaffrey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5450_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between the subject and the predicate in this statement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5450_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the purpose of stating someone's name as fact?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5450_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does this statement contribute to our understanding of Todd McCaffrey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5450_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5450_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Todd McCaffrey's name is Todd McCaffrey\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the context information contains a little-known fact about Todd McCaffrey, which states that \"Okay, some people know that I was born Todd Johnson.\" This suggests that Todd McCaffrey's birth name is indeed not \"Todd McCaffrey\", but rather \"Todd Johnson\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state \"What is Todd Mccaffrey's address?\" and provide an address for someone named Todd Mccaffrey. Additionally, the query directly asks if \"Todd McCaffrey's name is Todd McCaffrey,\" which is confirmed by the presence of multiple references to this individual in the provided context. Therefore, the information supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim \"Todd McCaffrey's name is Todd McCaffrey\" is wrong because the information provided indicates that Todd McCaffrey was born as Todd Johnson and later changed his last name to McCaffrey.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}